an hour in an hour anymore. They've
changed the way time works, and I can
prove it to you. This is a 1967 Almanac
that details the working minutes
required to buy selected foodstuffs in
1958. Check this out. Kilogram of beef
1958,
44 minutes to earn 2.2 lb of sirloin.
What's 2 and 1/2 lb of sirloin cost
today? It also shows you how consumers
spent their dollar in 1965. How long did
you have to work for healthcare in 1965?
80 hours according to this. In 2026, 967
hours. 1,109% increase. What about
college tuition? 1965, 100 hours. 2026,
hours. Child care 1965, 120 hours. 2026,
867 hours. 623%
more. Housing, here's a shocker. 1965,
8,000 hours. 2026, 28,000
hours.
Transportation, your new car 1965, 1,060
hours. 2026, 3,200 hours. What about a
tank of gas? 1965, 1.2 hours. 2026, 3
hours. 150% increase. Median rent, 1965,
44 hours. 2026, 100 hours. What about a
1 lb loaf of bread? 1965, 5 minutes.
2026, 8 minutes. Groceries as a whole
1965, you had to work 10 hours. 2026,
you had to work 13 hours. Dude, this is
crazy when you look at the data. We have
to pay so much more for the same things
we've always gotten, and our food is of
such a bad quality it makes our
healthcare skyrocket. Over 1,100%
increase in 60 years. This whole book is
why I bought land is cuz I can see
there's no future in continuing to earn
money to buy things of increasing value
with diminishing returns in a system
that does not give a [__] about us. What
do you think the 2067 Almanac's going to
look like?